<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Colorado Springs Real Estate Video Blog with Jason Daniels</title>
    <description>Our mission at Finch &amp; Gable is to be your best resource for Colorado Springs real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Finch &amp; Gable, your professional Colorado Springs Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 13:58:20 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 13:58:20 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Understanding Zillow’s Zestimates</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/MACIbnRn1nE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Zestimate should only function as a starting point for your home&amp;rsquo;s value.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can you trust Zillow’s Zestimates?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The short answer is no—whether you’re buying or selling, they should only be used as a starting point&lt;/strong&gt;. Roughly 75% of the Zestimates in Colorado are inaccurate. Even Zillow states that their Zestimates are off by an average of 5%, and we’ve found that the average is usually closer to 10%. That means if the average sale price in your area is $400,000, the Zestimate for any home could be off by as much as $40,000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=We’d be happy to meet with you, go over the numbers, and give you a free, accurate valuation of your home.%20http://localhost:4000/understanding-zillows-zestimates.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“We’d be happy to meet with you, go over the numbers, and give you a free, accurate valuation of your home.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zillow relies on public and user-submitted data to calculate their Zestimates, which means that anyone can artificially inflate their home’s value on Zillow’s website. Think of it this way: If you weren’t feeling well and went to WebMD to give yourself a diagnosis, that might work if you have something as simple as a cold. If you have a serious health concern, though, you’ll probably reach out to a doctor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s why, &lt;strong&gt;if you really want to know what your home is worth, you’re better off reaching out to a real estate agent&lt;/strong&gt;. Here at Finch &amp;amp; Gable, we’d be happy to meet with you, go over the numbers, and give you a free, accurate valuation of your home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to take us up on this offer, would like to know more about Zillow, or have any other real estate questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to us. I look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/understanding-zillows-zestimates.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/understanding-zillows-zestimates.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We’re Grateful for Your Support in 2020</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/uplNTgtLHGs?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thank you for your support this year.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2020 has been pretty tough; I know that many families still face challenges. We started this year rebranding as Finch &amp;amp; Gable—and then the pandemic hit. Due to that, we didn’t think we were going to launch this company. We’ve not only been through a pandemic but also all the political turmoil that’s come up this year. Nevertheless, we made it through, thanks to your support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s now the Christmas season, and we were able to help over 100 families buy or sell a home here in Colorado. We’re just blessed to have been a part of our clients’ lives. &lt;strong&gt;Merry Christmas and happy holidays!&lt;/strong&gt; We pray that your families will be blessed during the season as we have been and that you’re able to overcome whatever trials you face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there’s anything we can do for you, please reach out to us. See you in 2021!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/were-grateful-for-your-support-in-2020.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/were-grateful-for-your-support-in-2020.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Will the Election Impact the Market?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/JETOVvqwcrw?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;How will this presidential election affect the future of the real estate market?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This has been a crazy election year with a lot of strange things happening in the marketplace. So how will these events impact the upcoming real estate market? Both nationally and here in Colorado Springs, it’s not all doom and gloom—there is some good news in it all. There are four reasons why I think things will turn out okay:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. There’s a huge demand for millennial buyers&lt;/strong&gt;, who are driving the market across the U.S. We have many new job openings and opportunities coming into Colorado Springs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Mortgage rates are historically low&lt;/strong&gt;. The average is 2.85% for a 30-year fixed-rate, which is the lowest rates have ever been in recorded history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Things will likely slow down during the holidays and pick back up in the spring.%20http://localhost:4000/how-will-the-election-impact-the-market.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Things will likely slow down during the holidays and pick back up in the spring.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Home prices continue to appreciate&lt;/strong&gt; thanks to our low inventory and high demand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. History shows the market will calm down soon&lt;/strong&gt;. Experts have studied the market over the last 60 years with respect to presidential elections, and they found that it takes nearly a quarter before the market calms down; it just takes some time to get used to the new administration’s policies, especially those regarding housing finance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, things are likely going to turn out alright in the end. Experts are saying that interest rates should remain low throughout the year. There is some speculation about how a COVID vaccine might affect things, but ultimately, things will likely slow down during the holidays and pick back up in the spring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The United States of America is the greatest country on Earth. We have a very resilient economy, and the people are resilient as well, especially here in Colorado Springs. I just know that 2021 is going to be a great year, and not just for real estate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about the current or future market or you’re looking to buy or sell a house, don’t hesitate to reach out to us. We’d love to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-will-the-election-impact-the-market.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-will-the-election-impact-the-market.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Will We See You at Our Pumpkin Patch Event?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/BdedYLYCZgI?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Our upcoming pumpkin patch event is fall fun for the whole family.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today it’s my great pleasure to be able to invite you to &lt;strong&gt;a day at the pumpkin patch on October 10 at the &lt;u&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot; href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/rEhmsiT4yBast3Ks6&quot;&gt;Western Mining Museum&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (225 North Gate Blvd). From 9 a.m. to noon, we’ll have games and plenty of other fun activities for the whole family to enjoy. Plus, each family member gets to take home a free pumpkin!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tickets for the museum may be purchased separately, but are not included in the Pumpkin Patch entrance. Please bring masks per the mandate of the Governor (masks only have to be worn inside) and practice social distancing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;to-rsvp-click-here&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To RSVP, &lt;u&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot; href=&quot;http://vid.us/n2mhzj&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can also reply to the email that led you to this page, give our office a call at (719) 999-8900, or send an email to &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:events@finchandgable.com&quot;&gt;events@finchandgable.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt; by October 6&lt;/strong&gt;. If you have any questions, feel free to reach out to us as well. We hope to see you there.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/will-we-see-you-at-our-pumpkin-patch-event.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/will-we-see-you-at-our-pumpkin-patch-event.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Does Our Green Photo Initiative Help Winter Sellers?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/T0sUxana1CU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;By using our Green Photo Initiative, our winter home sellers will stand out amid the competition.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you’re thinking of listing your home this coming winter, our Green Photo Initiative will help it sell quickly and for top dollar. With this initiative, &lt;strong&gt;we’ll send a professional photographer to your house to take pictures of its exterior and capture its beauty while your lawn is still green and landscaping still in bloom.&lt;/strong&gt; We’ll then hold onto these photos for you until you find your next home and are ready to list. You need a professional photographer who knows how to make people want your home, and we know several such photographers we can send your way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year, we were able to help many sellers maximize their exposure by using this strategy. When your home goes on the market in November, December, January, or February, it will stand out among the other listings that have drab, dreary winter pictures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you’d like to sign up for this initiative, just call or email the Finch &amp;amp; Gable Real Estate Company anytime.&lt;/strong&gt; If you have any other real estate needs, feel free to reach out to us as well. We’d love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 09:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-does-our-green-photo-initiative-help-winter-sellers.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-does-our-green-photo-initiative-help-winter-sellers.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Would Our Market Handle Another Outbreak?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/pXnv3kWrQww?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;If another COVID outbreak happens, here&amp;rsquo;s how our market will handle it.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What will our real estate market look like if we go through another outbreak of the coronavirus? We’re receiving this question a lot. 2020 has been very uncertain, but from what I’ve seen, I have good news on this front.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the first outbreak, there was a government-mandated shutdown, people were stuck in their homes, and businesses were temporarily closing. From what I’ve heard, another shutdown enforced by the government is unlikely because it had such a huge economic impact. Afterward, we saw a V-shaped recovery, which is great news. It’s called a V-shape recovery because the economy went down quickly, then rebounded sharply, much like the letter ‘V.’ &lt;strong&gt;If the economy declines again, we will likely see another upward rebound shortly thereafter&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s why: We have been selling about 1,200 to 1,400 houses monthly for the last couple of months, and there are currently just over 1,100 properties on the market in the Pikes Peak region. &lt;strong&gt;We’re seeing a ton of pent-up demand&lt;/strong&gt;, though the rate of new home construction can’t keep up. Building materials and appliances can’t be delivered as quickly as before (for example, General Electric switched to making ventilators during this time). Also, no one knows what will happen after the presidential election.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If the economy declines again, we will likely see another upward rebound shortly thereafter.%20http://localhost:4000/how-would-our-market-handle-another-outbreak.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If the economy declines again, we will likely see another upward rebound shortly thereafter.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, there’s still plenty of demand. If the pandemic hits hard again, we may see things slow down for a season. It may take until next spring or summer to fully recover, but our local economy is healthy and will persevere. We have strong employment and military here, and people are commuting from Denver and purchasing homes. &lt;strong&gt;We have a solid outlook, even if we take a few more punches&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have specific questions or are considering selling your house, please reach out via phone or email. If you’re thinking about buying a home, we currently have interest rates under 3% for a 30-year fixed mortgage for the first time ever. Whatever your needs are, we’d love to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-would-our-market-handle-another-outbreak.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-would-our-market-handle-another-outbreak.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are We Still Having Our Annual BBQ?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/1_e9NNrtzBE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;The spirit of our annual barbecue persists; here&amp;rsquo;s what you need to know.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You’ve been emailed this video message because you’re a special VIP client and we wanted to thank you for your business over the years. This is normally the month when we do our annual barbecue catered by &lt;u&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot; href=&quot;https://rudysbbq.com/location/detail/colorado-springs-co&quot;&gt;Rudy&amp;rsquo;s Bar-B-Q&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;, but we’ve had to cancel a lot of our events this year due to COVID-19. We miss seeing you, so we’ve decided to shake things up: We’re bringing the barbecue to you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The first 10 people who reply to this email with “Howdy, partner” will win a gift bag and a $50 gift card to Rudy’s&lt;/strong&gt;. This way, you’ll still be able to have your own barbecue at home! Inside the custom Finch and Gable couture gift bag will be a pack of IBC root beer (always a crowd-pleaser), some beef jerky to tide you over until you pick up that Rudy’s meal, and an extra-large bottle of Rudy’s Bar-B-Q sauce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, in September, we’ll be announcing the winner of our referral contest. You still have time to send us some referrals so you can be crowned the person who’s sent the most since last August! Competition is still close; a few of you are neck-and-neck at the moment. Please consider any friends or family members who are thinking about buying or selling a home. We’d love to help them achieve their real estate goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, hit that reply button and shoot us a ‘Howdy, partner!’ The only stipulation is one prize set per household. If you have questions or needs concerning real estate, just tag that greeting onto your email explaining your situation, and we’ll be happy to talk with you. We’re always here to be your resource.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/are-we-still-having-our-annual-bbq.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/are-we-still-having-our-annual-bbq.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Which 3 Upgrades Should You Avoid If You’re Preparing to Sell?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/4uBAidZ4Kdw?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;There are three upgrades you must avoid if you&amp;rsquo;re selling soon.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you’re selling your home in the next few years, here are the top three upgrades you should avoid making:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. An outdoor swimming pool&lt;/strong&gt;. Here in Colorado you can only use an outdoor pool for about four months out of the year. They’re fun and exciting to have, but they’re also expensive to maintain and considered an extra liability. A lot of buyers are simply turned off by pools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Solar panels&lt;/strong&gt;. Solar panel technology is constantly improving and becoming less expensive, but if you install panels on your home, you won’t get a full return on your investment in the short term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Expensive landscaping&lt;/strong&gt;. For example, if you build any water features and/or large retaining walls you’ll be lucky to get a 25% return on value when you sell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re curious about which upgrades will fetch the best sale price for your home, give my team and me a call and we’d be happy to schedule a quick walk-through. If you have questions about any other real estate topics, feel free to give me a call as well. We’re here to help.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/which-3-upgrades-should-you-avoid-if-youre-preparing-to-sell.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/which-3-upgrades-should-you-avoid-if-youre-preparing-to-sell.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s the Difference Between Buying New or Resale?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/bX4JCDtreqA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m explaining how buying a newly built home is different from resale.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many clients have asked what differentiates buying a newly built home from a resale, so I’m diving into that topic today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, with a new build, you get that brand-new feeling, the ability to choose the colors and finishes, and &lt;strong&gt;a 12-month warranty for everything in the house&lt;/strong&gt; (sometimes the structural warranty lasts years). The procedure is also a bit different. You will need a real estate agent who knows the new construction process well to help guide you through it. There are different construction walk-throughs including frame or pre-drywall walks and final walks, and you need someone who knows what to look for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another great thing about purchasing a new construction home is that there’s less competition for them. Currently here in Colorado, &lt;strong&gt;we receive multiple offers on resale homes, and it’s a fight to win it&lt;/strong&gt;. However, with new construction, you’re locking in a lot, and building it from the ground up. A new construction home will also appreciate during the six to 12 months it’s being worked on, and appreciation rates are as high as 6% to 10% right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=You will need a real estate agent who knows the new construction process well.%20http://localhost:4000/whats-the-difference-between-buying-new-or-resale.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“You will need a real estate agent who knows the new construction process well.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you buy a resale home, you hire an inspector to come look at the house and negotiate repairs with the seller, whereas with new construction there’s a warranty, and you don’t have to worry as much about things breaking. Additionally, the newer the home, the more updated its safety will be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember: Hire a professional agent to help you. &lt;strong&gt;They can negotiate upgrades and lot premiums&lt;/strong&gt;, and they’ll help you check out all the different builders in town or the area you want to live in so you know exactly what you’re getting in the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or need a Realtor, give us a call or send an email. We look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/whats-the-difference-between-buying-new-or-resale.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/whats-the-difference-between-buying-new-or-resale.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What You Need to Know About Colorado Real Estate Right Now</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/gSEWS8BvyIQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Our market is ripe for buyers and sellers; here are corroborating facts.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now that we’ve reached the end of our stay-at-home orders here in Colorado, many people are wondering what the current condition of real estate is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pent-up buyer demand is primed to explode; even with virtual tours during quarantine, we were seeing multiple-offer scenarios left and right. Six months’ worth or more of inventory is considered a buyer’s market, while anything under six months is a seller’s market—&lt;strong&gt;we’re still firmly in a seller’s market&lt;/strong&gt;. For homes priced at $500,000 or below, we only have roughly 2.5 months’ worth of inventory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-you-need-to-know-about-colorado-real-estate-right-now.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-you-need-to-know-about-colorado-real-estate-right-now.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
