<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Colorado Springs Real Estate Video Blog with Jason Daniels</title>
    <description>Our mission at Finch &amp; Gable is to be your best resource for Colorado Springs real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Finch &amp; Gable, your professional Colorado Springs Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 14:22:04 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 14:22:04 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Which 3 Upgrades Should You Avoid If You’re Preparing to Sell?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/4uBAidZ4Kdw?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;There are three upgrades you must avoid if you&amp;rsquo;re selling soon.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you’re selling your home in the next few years, here are the top three upgrades you should avoid making:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. An outdoor swimming pool&lt;/strong&gt;. Here in Colorado you can only use an outdoor pool for about four months out of the year. They’re fun and exciting to have, but they’re also expensive to maintain and considered an extra liability. A lot of buyers are simply turned off by pools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Solar panels&lt;/strong&gt;. Solar panel technology is constantly improving and becoming less expensive, but if you install panels on your home, you won’t get a full return on your investment in the short term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Expensive landscaping&lt;/strong&gt;. For example, if you build any water features and/or large retaining walls you’ll be lucky to get a 25% return on value when you sell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re curious about which upgrades will fetch the best sale price for your home, give my team and me a call and we’d be happy to schedule a quick walk-through. If you have questions about any other real estate topics, feel free to give me a call as well. We’re here to help.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/which-3-upgrades-should-you-avoid-if-youre-preparing-to-sell.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/which-3-upgrades-should-you-avoid-if-youre-preparing-to-sell.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s the Difference Between Buying New or Resale?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/bX4JCDtreqA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m explaining how buying a newly built home is different from resale.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many clients have asked what differentiates buying a newly built home from a resale, so I’m diving into that topic today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, with a new build, you get that brand-new feeling, the ability to choose the colors and finishes, and &lt;strong&gt;a 12-month warranty for everything in the house&lt;/strong&gt; (sometimes the structural warranty lasts years). The procedure is also a bit different. You will need a real estate agent who knows the new construction process well to help guide you through it. There are different construction walk-throughs including frame or pre-drywall walks and final walks, and you need someone who knows what to look for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another great thing about purchasing a new construction home is that there’s less competition for them. Currently here in Colorado, &lt;strong&gt;we receive multiple offers on resale homes, and it’s a fight to win it&lt;/strong&gt;. However, with new construction, you’re locking in a lot, and building it from the ground up. A new construction home will also appreciate during the six to 12 months it’s being worked on, and appreciation rates are as high as 6% to 10% right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=You will need a real estate agent who knows the new construction process well.%20http://localhost:4000/whats-the-difference-between-buying-new-or-resale.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“You will need a real estate agent who knows the new construction process well.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you buy a resale home, you hire an inspector to come look at the house and negotiate repairs with the seller, whereas with new construction there’s a warranty, and you don’t have to worry as much about things breaking. Additionally, the newer the home, the more updated its safety will be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember: Hire a professional agent to help you. &lt;strong&gt;They can negotiate upgrades and lot premiums&lt;/strong&gt;, and they’ll help you check out all the different builders in town or the area you want to live in so you know exactly what you’re getting in the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or need a Realtor, give us a call or send an email. We look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/whats-the-difference-between-buying-new-or-resale.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/whats-the-difference-between-buying-new-or-resale.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What You Need to Know About Colorado Real Estate Right Now</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/gSEWS8BvyIQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Our market is ripe for buyers and sellers; here are corroborating facts.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now that we’ve reached the end of our stay-at-home orders here in Colorado, many people are wondering what the current condition of real estate is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pent-up buyer demand is primed to explode; even with virtual tours during quarantine, we were seeing multiple-offer scenarios left and right. Six months’ worth or more of inventory is considered a buyer’s market, while anything under six months is a seller’s market—&lt;strong&gt;we’re still firmly in a seller’s market&lt;/strong&gt;. For homes priced at $500,000 or below, we only have roughly 2.5 months’ worth of inventory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-you-need-to-know-about-colorado-real-estate-right-now.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-you-need-to-know-about-colorado-real-estate-right-now.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Message of Encouragement Amid Uncertainty</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/N824gcJQRoU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Although this pandemic has changed our daily lives for the time being, it has also allowed us to focus on what&amp;rsquo;s most important.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During this time of uncertainty, we believe &lt;strong&gt;it’s also a time for growth&lt;/strong&gt;: A time to reflect on what’s really important, be creative, have faith, and love our neighbors. It has taken a crisis to make time for home, but when you’re ready, we’re here to help you find yours.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-message-of-encouragement-amid-uncertainty.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/a-message-of-encouragement-amid-uncertainty.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Changes in Our Market Since 2008</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/foMJfAO-XsA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to Buy a Home? Search All Homes
Want to Sell a Home? Get a Home Value Report&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How has the real estate market changed since the crash of 2008? It hasn’t changed a whole lot, but the minor changes that have been enacted were done so for good reason. Lending restrictions, for example, have tightened. To find out what other changes you need to be aware of, watch this short video.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 08:54:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/changes-in-our-market-since-2008.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/changes-in-our-market-since-2008.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Buying a Home Will Cost You</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZTTeXs3zy68?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to Buy a Home? Search All Homes
Want to Sell a Home? Get a Home Value Report&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How much money do you need to buy a house? The good news is, there are plenty of home financing options for you to choose from. How much cash you need depends on the type of financing you use. To find out more about what your options are, watch this short video.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 08:47:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-buying-home-will-cost-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-buying-home-will-cost-you.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Your Property Taxes Affect Your Monthly Payments</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ED0SpfEnUWg?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s what soon-to-be homeowners should know about their property taxes. Instead of paying them directly to the government, you pay your mortgage company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to Buy a Home? Search All Homes
Want to Sell a Home? Get a Home Value Report&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How exactly do property taxes affect your monthly mortgage payment? Most lenders require that they pay your taxes by placing some of your closing cost money in an escrow account. This ensures that the government won’t place a lien on the property before the mortgage company does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Once the lender calculates your tax bill, they divide it by 12 and add it to your monthly payment%20http://localhost:4000/how-your-property-taxes-affect-your.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Once the lender calculates your tax bill, they divide it by 12 and add it to your monthly payment”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Via an estimate from the county, your lender will figure out what your tax estimate is. Taxes are due April 15, but here in Colorado, property taxes are paid in arrears, meaning that your taxes don’t have to be paid in their entirety by April 15. Specifically, the state allows you to pay the first half of what you owe in taxes in February, and the second half in June.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many mortgage companies prefer this method because it allows them to hold on to your money and keep the interest. Once the lender calculates your tax bill, they divide it by 12 and add it to your monthly payment, splitting it up nicely over the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re using an online mortgage calculator, make sure you’re including taxes and homeowner’s insurance because those will most certainly affect your monthly payment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have more questions about this topic, or you’re ready to start looking at homes, feel free to reach out to me via phone or email. You can also check out the latest Pike’s Peak area homes by following the links below.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 11:43:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-your-property-taxes-affect-your.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-your-property-taxes-affect-your.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reasons Real Estate Deals Can Fall Apart</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/shi0d2wMfPA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I’m explaining the three main reasons real estate deals fall apart.
Want to Buy a Home? Search All Homes
Want to Sell a Home? Get a Home Value Report&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I want to explain the three main reasons why real estate deals fall apart. Some of these deal-breakers are avoidable, some are not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Financing.&lt;/strong&gt; If the buyer is having financial difficulties, like not getting the proper documentation to the lender or having issues with income, a deal can fall apart. There are many reasons financing can fall through.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Some of these deal-breakers are avoidable, some are not.%20http://localhost:4000/reasons-real-estate-deals-can-fall-apart.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Some of these deal-breakers are avoidable, some are not.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Problem with the property.&lt;/strong&gt; If a problem with the property is found during the inspection, like a major issue with the roof or furnace that the seller is not willing to address, that can often lead to the deal falling apart. However, if you’re the seller, you have to disclose that information to the next buyer, so it always makes sense to keep the first deal together. As a buyer, if there are multiple offers on the home, you need to decide if it makes sense to cancel the deal if it’s not going to cost you that much to fix it yourself. Your Realtor can help with this decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Cold feet.&lt;/strong&gt; Sometimes a buyer gets cold feet and backs out of the deal, or sometimes they find a house they like better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions please reach out by phone or email. We would love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 09:16:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/reasons-real-estate-deals-can-fall-apart.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/reasons-real-estate-deals-can-fall-apart.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Role Do Escrow Accounts Play in a Home Sale?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/dufdzRaTqGI?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re confused about what an escrow account is, today I’ll provide a quick definition.
Want to Buy a Home? Search All Homes
Want to Sell a Home? Get a Home Value Report&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is an escrow account?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An escrow account is what a mortgage company sets up when buyers get a loan to purchase a house. The account is comprised of funds that don’t apply to the principal or interest of your mortgage. In other words, they’ll go toward your property taxes and homeowners insurance. The payment for setting up your escrow account is included in the closing costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every time you make a monthly payment to your mortgage company, they’ll take a piece of that check and put it into your escrow account. Usually, homeowners insurance is billed annually, so your mortgage company will use your escrow account to pay your bill when it’s due. That’s why your insurance company actually sends your mortgage company the bill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Every time you make a monthly payment to your mortgage company, they’ll take a piece of that check and put it into your escrow account.%20http://localhost:4000/what-role-do-escrow-accounts-play-in.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Every time you make a monthly payment to your mortgage company, they’ll take a piece of that check and put it into your escrow account.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here in Colorado, property taxes are paid in arrears, which means you can pay them in April, or pay half in February and half in June. Most mortgage companies prefer to split the payment. That way, after they make the first payment in February, they can collect interest on it until June.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it’s time to sell your home, a lot of sellers have one question in particular at the closing table: Why is the title company billing me for taxes if I already paid them through my mortgage company? When you pay taxes to your mortgage company, those funds aren’t sent to the county—they’re held in your account. When you sell your home, to ensure there are no tax judgments against the new owner, the title company has to collect them from you at closing. You can either pay out of your equity or write them a check.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mortgage company will then mail you a check three or four weeks after closing, so make sure they have your new forwarding address so you can get that money back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, if you have questions about this or any other real estate topic, or you’re thinking of buying or selling a home soon, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d be happy to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 11:32:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-role-do-escrow-accounts-play-in.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-role-do-escrow-accounts-play-in.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What To Look for When You're Walking Through a Home</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ofVp5RlFR0Y?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you’re walking through a home you’re considering for purchase, what things should you keep an eye out for? Today I’ll tell you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to Buy a Home? Search All Homes
Want to Sell a Home? Get a Home Value Report&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you’re touring a resale listing you’re interested in purchasing, look at the windows, doors, ceilings, and other areas of the home for signs of structural damage. Check to see if there’s any cracked drywall, water damage, rust on the water heater, or drainage coming from the air conditioning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pay attention to the plumbing, too, especially if you live in Colorado Springs: Polybutylene pipes used in house construction in the 1980s have been known to burst.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll also want to take a walk around outside the home to check for cracks in the brick, siding, or foundation walls. See if your roof is made with t-lock shingles, as the whole roof will need replacing if any of them are damaged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Don’t get caught up in the aesthetics of the house.%20http://localhost:4000/what-to-look-for-when-youre-walking.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Don’t get caught up in the aesthetics of the house.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Above all, make sure that you’re working with a knowledgeable Realtor. You don’t want to take the time to write an offer on a home that has a host of hidden, potentially costly issues that will cause problems down the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a background in construction management, and my team has been trained to know just what to look for. We’ll also help you schedule a home inspection for a home you’re interested in purchasing; a home inspector will go through the whole house to assess the condition of the property.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, don’t get caught up in the aesthetics of the house. Ugly carpets can be replaced, and shiny new appliances don’t necessarily mean the whole house is that new or stable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about buying a home, including what to look for as you walk through a showing, don’t hesitate to reach out to us. We’d be glad to help you ensure that your next purchase goes off without a hitch.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:07:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-to-look-for-when-youre-walking.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-to-look-for-when-youre-walking.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
